

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

🔀 hughsin23@gmail.com

6

0407-320-427



Melbourne



linkedin.com/in/hsinclair23/



github.com/Hughsin23



SUMMARY

I'm a former tech retail sales expert, transitioning into a Software Engineering career, having completed a Software Engineering immersive in 2022. I love helping others find tech solutions, and this new branch of career will help me create some of those solutions instead of just knowing about them!



WORK EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

INSTRUCTIONAL ASSISTANT MAR 2022 - AUGUEST 2022

- Creating warmup exercises for various technical levels, ensuring talented students were extended and less experienced students were motivated with achievable tasks.
- · Assisting students with technical issues, coaching, mentoring and support as they learn to code.
- · Guiding students to find their own solutions.
- · Working with head instructor to maintain class flow, while monitoring student needs.
- · Creating and maintaining a Gitbook with class notes and revision for students to return to.

General Assembly

SOFTWARE ENGINEER NOV 2021-FEB 2022

- Completed over 500 hours of progressional training over thirteen weeks.
- Developed a portfolio showcasing various computer languages such as CSS, HTML, Javascript and Ruby.
- Worked within a small team to demonstrate concepts learned over the course of the thirteen weeks.

Officeworks

TECH SPECIALIST NOV 2020 - NOV 2021

- Assisted clients with finding technical solutions for local networking, router/modem setup.
- · Worked with other tech specialists to quickly resolve any issues that occurred onsite.
- · Managed the training of other co-workers in tech areas to address any gaps in knowledge.



COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

JCV (Japan Club Victoria)

VOLUNTEER 2015-PRESENT

Volunteer at multiple events per year, helping run festival events etc.



SKILLS

Javascript | VS Code | React | HTML | CSS Ruby | Sinatra | GitHub | Node | Rails | MongoDB | Bilingual (Japanese)



PROJECTS

Tic Tac Toe

Show us your Quack

Safehaven



EDUCATION

Software Engineering (Immersive)

GENERAL ASSEMBLY 2021-2022

Bachelor of Arts - International Studies

RMIT UNIVERSITY 2016-2020

- RMIT mentoring program
- RMIT cultural exchange program

Diploma of Languages (Japanese Intensive)

RMIT UNIVERSITY 2015-2015